{
    "id": "312410fe4d3f4e2ea5061d2028fbe903",
    "title": "Gap Filling Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I have lived in cities so I …………………………….. the noise.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am used to",
                "am using to",
                "used to"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It wasn’t easy for me to get ……………………………… up in the middle of the night.",
            "description": "An ing form or a noun is used after get used to or be used to.",
            "answers": [
                "used to getting",
                "used to get",
                "used getting"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………………… smoke, but now he doesn’t.",
            "description": "We use used to to talk about past habits. ",
            "answers": [
                "used to",
                "is used to",
                "has used to"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………………. living alone.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "used to",
                "am used to",
                "am using to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "When I was a child, I …………………………….. watch a lot of movies.",
            "description": "Used to shows past habits.",
            "answers": [
                "was used to",
                "used to",
                "got used to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………………………. he was feeling better.",
            "description": "That can be dropped after said.",
            "answers": [
                "said",
                "said that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………………… she was lying.",
            "description": "That can be dropped after think.",
            "answers": [
                "thought",
                "thought that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………………………. I should wait a little longer.",
            "description": "That can be dropped after suggest. ",
            "answers": [
                "suggested",
                "suggested that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………………………. he was not coming.",
            "description": "That cannot be dropped after reply.",
            "answers": [
                "replied",
                "replied that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She………………………………. she was busy.",
            "description": "That cannot be dropped after shout.",
            "answers": [
                "shouted",
                "shouted that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "No one paid attention to the ……………………………………. the child felt lonely at home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "fact",
                "fact that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You can borrow my car ……………………………. you bring it back tomorrow.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "provided",
                "provided that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}